So we're getting started with Microsoft Designer,
also known as one of the best tools,
one of the, some people believe that it is the best,
but it's very heavy to use for a tool.
But I can say, and we can say,
one of the best design tools available out there,
one of the best AI design tools available out there,
Microsoft Designer.
So as you're probably aware,
Microsoft also has another AI tool,
which is called co-pilot, Microsoft's co-pilot.
So when it comes to Microsoft co-pilot,
that's another AI tool that is purely text-based,
and focused on text, and it's a chatbot, we can say.
It's more of a chatbot.
But when it comes to Microsoft Designer,
it's specifically and especially made and build for designers,
and for designing purposes, for whatever it is,
designing posters, designing advertisement,
and marketing materials, designing blog posts,
designing, I don't know, backgrounds,
wallpapers, whatever that you make come to your mind,
you can do with Microsoft Designer today.
So we're going to go through it.